redhotpie.com.au 2019-07-07

# Online dating privacy policy on RedHotPie

## Email Address and Consent

Please ensure that your address is valid and able to accept mail. Your address will never be passed on to third parties.

By joining RedHotPie you consent to RedHotPie emailing you. If you do not wish to receive emails, you can 'opt-out' of any or all of them by updating your preferences in ‘Email Notifications’.

Add RedHotPie to your safe senders list (click here for instructions)

## Our Commitment To Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

In our online **ANONYMOUS** registration form, we ask you to provide us with certain information such as your email, age and the type of relationship you are looking for. **However, NONE of the personally identifiable information can be accessed or used by the public to identify a specific individual.**

In the course of using our site, we may track certain information such as your IP addresses and email addresses, phone number. Many sites automatically collect this information. If you choose to post messages in our Message Boards, chat rooms, or other message areas, we will only display such information about you as you choose to reveal. 

If you send us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, or if other users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities or postings on the site, we may collect such information into a file which is only accessed by authorized personnel. We may also collect other users' comments about you in our complaints department. 

## The Way We Use Information:

We internally use personally identifiable information of our users to improve our marketing efforts, to statistically analyze site usage, to improve our content and product offerings as well as to customize our site's content and layout. We believe these uses allow us to improve our site and better tailor your online experience to meet your needs. 

We may also use personally identifiable information about you to deliver information to you that, in some cases, are targeted to your interests, such as targeted banners and promotions. 

We use personally identifiable information to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our User Agreement. 

We DO NOT sell or rent any personally identifiable information about you to any third party without your permission. We do disclose information in aggregate to advertisers and for other marketing and promotional purposes. However, in these situations, we DO NOT disclose to these entities any information that could be used to personally identify you. Certain information, such as your password, credit card number, and bank account number, are not disclosed in aggregate at all. 

We may use your e-mail to send you messages that you have request and to respond to any feedback or queries about out Site or Services. 

## Marketing and Promotional Messages

All marketing or promotional messages sent from redhotpie.com.au will be only sent if you have signified your consent via the explicit opt-in process. 

## Opt-out / Unsubscribing

redhotpie.com.au will not send you any messages that you have not requested. To opt-out please use one of the following methods: 

1\. All messages sent to you from RedHotPie contain an opt-out option or a link to the unsubscribe function.   
2\. You can unsubscribe by logging into your account via Manage Account / Profile screen.   
3\. You can at any time access the unsubscribe system to stop all messages send to an email address (located here).   
4\. You can send an email, via our help system, telling us you wish to stop all messages (located here or [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#365e535a46764453525e5942465f531855595b185743)). 

## Our Commitment To Data Security

RedHotPie has security measures in place to protect and prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. RedHotPie uses industry standard efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal identifiable information such as firewalls. While "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet, our technical experts at RedHotPie work hard to ensure your secure use of our services. 

## How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information:

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by logging in to RedHotPie and going to "Manage Account / Profile" page. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information where you are the only one who has full access and control of your information. 

RedHotPie Members have the following choices to modify or delete their information from our database:

1\. Send an email to our customer service rep. at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#b6ded3dac6f6c4d3d2ded9c2c6dfd398d5d9db98d7c3)  
2\. Log in with your password and modify/delete your profile

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

## Important Notice

As a responsible corporate citizen RedHotPie cooperates with the proper judicial processes at both the State and Federal level.  RedHotPie will, upon receipt of an appropriate warrant, or other judicial order, provide information to state and federal prosecuting authorities.
